<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Jessica Huynh</title>
    <link>/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Jessica Huynh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 22:22:26 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Gỏi cuốn and peanut sauce recipe</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/07/goi-cuon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 22:22:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/07/goi-cuon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gỏi cuốn are Vietnamese spring rolls; they&amp;rsquo;re easy to make, especially for group things. This is an appropriate-for-cheap-college students version of a recipe I learned from my mom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not giving any particular amounts because I never measure things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;vietnamese-spring-rolls-gỏi-cuốn&#34;&gt;Vietnamese spring rolls (Gỏi cuốn)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bánh tráng (rice paper wrappers)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Miến (mung bean and potato noodles); in the US they&amp;rsquo;re often in a tell-tale pink mesh wrap. If you can&amp;rsquo;t find them, regular rice noodles will do&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sliced cucumbers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grated carrots&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lettuce or cabbage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Generally, about 10 ounces of noodles will serve for a packet of wrappers. One grated carrot can usually do around 5 goi cuon. Cucumbers vary a little bit more but one cucumber per about ten goi cuon works for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also add, depending on dietary requirements and restrictions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cooked shrimp (most traditional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chicken (I marinate with soy sauce, lemon, ginger, and garlic in some proportion I haven&amp;rsquo;t figured out yet)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tofu&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re fancy and have money (neither apply for me), the most traditional things to add are pork slices called chả and/or poached beef. Egg is also a popular option, although I&amp;rsquo;ve never tried it myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure everything is cut and sliced properly and fill a large bowl with water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wet the wrapper in the bowl of water by dipping one part in, then turning it in a circle all the way around&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lay the wrapper on a plate and at the very bottom of the wrapper towards you, lay some lettuce/cabbage pointing horizontally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Layer the noodles, cucumber, and cabbage on top&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fold over the wrapper from the bottom so that it covers just the ingredients you&amp;rsquo;ve added&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you have a meat or tofu to add, place them in a row just above the folded-over portion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fold the sides of the wrapper over so that nothing can escape&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From the bottom, now that the sides are folded over to contain the filling, continue rolling until everything is rolled up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repeat for as many spring rolls as you want&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;peanut-sauce&#34;&gt;Peanut sauce&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know the ingredients look fishy but I swear this tastes just as good as anything you&amp;rsquo;ll find in a restaurant or bakery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients-1&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Peanut butter (chunky or not doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tương đen (Hoison sauce)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Garlic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tương ớt tỏi (Vietnamese chili garlic sauce)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Water&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do two tablespoons of hoison sauce and peanut butter for every cup of water. You can add sugar and mashed up peanuts too, if that&amp;rsquo;s your preference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions-1&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Put in the peanut butter and hoison sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add water and stir until the peanut butter clumps are no longer visible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add as much garlic and chili sauce as you feel appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Hugo</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/05/migrating-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 16:43:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/05/migrating-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve begun the processing of migrating my blog posts from WordPress over to &lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;, a static site generator. I just hand migrated the lengthiest posts (the image galleries I can do later when I figure out a good way to associate images with particular posts). Layout is all new, all improved!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting out with Discover Deis</title>
      <link>/blog/2015/08/starting-out-with-discover-deis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015/08/starting-out-with-discover-deis/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;For the past nine weeks, I’ve been a member of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sites.google.com/a/brandeis.edu/jbs-2015-cosi/&#34;&gt;Voice, Mobile, and Web Application Development Justice Brandeis Semester&lt;/a&gt;, a program that helped us learn exactly what it seems like we should. Now that it’s over and done with, I’d like to look back on exactly how we got our app to where it is and some steps in the future we can take, because it’d be nice to make this a much more official app and fill out the empty spots in our already extensive database.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;brandeis-voice-tour&#34;&gt;Brandeis Voice Tour&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The program was nine weeks long, with the first five weeks devoted to classes (and working on our group project on Wednesdays) and the last four devoted to solely working on our project. The first two Wednesdays were devoted to team building with all the members of the JBS, followed by team formation and getting out the minimum viable product (MVP).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the group was originally formed, we were going to do hands-free navigation of public transportation. After some discussion, we switched to a voice tour app for Brandeis, partly because there was a higher chance of people getting to use it, and partly because hands-free navigation of public transit has already been done by larger groups than us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;data-collection-and-point-in-polygon-testing&#34;&gt;Data collection and point-in-polygon testing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this stage, we knew that there were about 150 or so buildings on campus. The question of how to detect what buildings the user was in or near came up, and the original thought was to start off with JSON objects (with one location per object), with a field that was an array of coordinates. In this array, we’d have four coordinates, and if your current location was less than this point but greater than this point, you’d be inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A better way soon came up. I came across an &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ecse.rpi.edu/Homepages/wrf/Research/Short_Notes/pnpoly.html&#34;&gt;implementation of point-in-polygon testing in C&lt;/a&gt; and decided to convert it to JavaScript. The way this works is that a ray is cast from the point (in this case your current location) through the polygon (the building’s vertices). If this ray intersects an odd number of times, you’re inside the location. If not, you’re outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;pointIncluded: function(vertices, current) {
    included = false;
    numVert = vertices.length;

    // create arrays of the x and y coordinates of the polygon
    var xArray = [];
    for (var i = 0; i &amp;amp;lt; numVert; i++) {
        xArray.push(vertices[i].x);
    }       
    var yArray = [];
    for (var i = 0; i &amp;amp;lt; numVert; i++) {
        yArray.push(vertices[i].y);
    }

    for (var i = 0, j = numVert - 1; i &amp;amp;lt; numVert; j = i++) { if ((yArray[i] &amp;amp;gt;= current.y) != (yArray[j] &amp;amp;gt;= current.y) &amp;amp;amp;&amp;amp;amp;
            (current.x &amp;amp;lt;= (xArray[j] - xArray[i]) * (current.y - yArray[i]) / (yArray[j] - yArray[i]) + xArray[i])) {
            included = !included;

        }
    }

    return included;
},
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The relevant bit is the third for-loop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;grabbing-the-distance&#34;&gt;Grabbing the distance&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that’s all well and good, but if you’re not in a location, it’d be nice to know how close you are to the closest location. To that end, we used a distance algorithm for coordinates (it’s not very interesting so I won’t show it; it’s in the GitHub if you’re really curious) that returns the distance between two points. In the interest of time and convenience, I wrote it so that the point of the location that is passed to the distance function is just the first element in that array of coordinates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;routing&#34;&gt;Routing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We initially tried it out on a set of about six locations on campus and the distance finding and point-in-polygon worked pretty well and this was the MVP we submitted after the first week as a group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next step was to route between locations and our first intuition (because I already had a bad feeling about having to get intersections’ coordinate data) was to write paths between each location that we had that was connected. Tianci found an implementation of single source, shortest path in JavaScript and we had routing working between our six locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;switching-to-a-navigation-app&#34;&gt;Switching to a navigation app&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout this process, part of the JBS was that we list features we would like in our app and do sprints and stories (as part of agile development, although I can’t say that many of the groups adhered very strictly to it) revolving around it. One issue we kept running into was feature bloat, wanting to add things like events nearby and classes at a location, along with a lot of arguing over what exactly would be on the home page. I was a big fan of a map and buttons and Ziyu thought that achievements and a profile would be good, to keep people coming back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I think the main issue, looking back on it, was that we all wanted something that people would use a lot. While tour apps are cool, they’re not something you use more than twice at most in your life. Adding events and achievements and such were a way to keep people coming back, or so the thinking went.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was the discussions/arguments over the home page that really brought this to light, because ideally you want the home page to reflect the primary purpose. For the first round of user feedback with the fellow members of this JBS, there was a lot of confusion about our home page design (just a carousel of images of different ‘types’ of tours) and a lot of people wanting to use it for navigation, which at the time was just a secondary purpose of the app. After all, if you can route between locations when you create your own tour, why not surface that as a separate function for people?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it was pretty clear at this point that navigation was a much better thing to work on, but we all had an inkling of the amount of data to collect and that put us off for a bit. We had another discussion and decided to focus on the self-guided tour and fixed tours with written descriptions, dropping the create your own tour feature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, as these things go, after that we had a discussion about maybe doing an informational app, since that would be more useful than a tour app and we’d be collecting mostly the same data. By this point, we had about fifty or so buildings in our set.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then someone went “since everyone in the first user feedback wanted to use it to navigate, and everyone we talked to would like a navigation app, let’s do a navigation app!” And I think next post, I’ll talk about some of the structure behind that and how we collected our data.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Sidebars in WordPress (again)</title>
      <link>/blog/2013/03/sidebars-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2013/03/sidebars-again/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;I figure it would be a good idea to repost my previous entry on custom sidebars in WordPress, partly for fun, partly to remind myself. This should work for any WordPress website on custom hosting (which means not WordPress.com blogs, unfortunately, unless there’s some magical way of getting at the code the Internet has yet to discover). I will be assuming you’re working off one of the WordPress default templates or can modify as needed on your own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;registering&#34;&gt;Registering&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deep in the WordPress theme files (that would be &lt;a href=&#34;http://yourblogurl/wp-contents/themes/themefolder&#34;&gt;http://yourblogurl/wp-contents/themes/themefolder&lt;/a&gt;), there is a file called functions.php. Open it with Notepad or something similar (or you can use the built-in editor, Appearance then Editor) and search for&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;function nevermind_widgets_init() {
    register_sidebar( array(
        &#39;name&#39; =&amp;gt; __( &#39;Main Sidebar&#39;, &#39;nevermind&#39; ),
        &#39;id&#39; =&amp;gt; &#39;sidebar-1&#39;,
        &#39;description&#39; =&amp;gt; __( &#39;Appears on posts and pages except the optional Front Page template, which has its own widgets&#39;, &#39;nevermind&#39; ),
        &#39;before_widget&#39; =&amp;gt; &#39;&amp;lt;aside id=&amp;quot;%1$s&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;widget %2$s&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&#39;,
        &#39;after_widget&#39; =&amp;gt; &#39;&amp;lt;/aside&amp;gt;&#39;,
        &#39;before_title&#39; =&amp;gt; &#39;&amp;lt;h3 class=&amp;quot;widget-title&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&#39;,
        &#39;after_title&#39; =&amp;gt; &#39;&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&#39;,
    ) );
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(‘nevermind’ is the name of my custom theme, because holy hell, I’m unoriginal; the default would be twentytwelve or twentyeleven)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There may be just the one, or there may be multiple bits of code like this, depending on your theme. This is actually (almost) the original snippet from the new Twenty Twelve theme. The function themename_widgets_init() initializes the little widgets you can place in your sidebar. Each register_sidebar() call does exactly what you would think it would, it registers the sidebar in question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-if-i-don-t-have-a-functions-php-file&#34;&gt;What if I don’t have a functions.php file?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check again and be sure, but if you don’t, just create a file called functions.php and stick &amp;lt;?php at the beginning of it, without whitespace, and follow along.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;breaking-register-sidebar-down&#34;&gt;Breaking register_sidebar() down&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A good resource, if you’re familiar with coding at all, is the WordPress codex, where there are pages of information about each function you could possibly want to know. To save you a click though, here’s what the codex says:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;?php register_sidebar( array(
    &#39;name&#39;          =&amp;gt; __( &#39;Sidebar name&#39;, &#39;theme_text_domain&#39; ),
    &#39;id&#39;            =&amp;gt; &#39;unique-sidebar-id&#39;,
    &#39;description&#39;   =&amp;gt; &#39;&#39;,
        &#39;class&#39;         =&amp;gt; &#39;&#39;,
    &#39;before_widget&#39; =&amp;gt; &#39;&amp;lt;li id=&amp;quot;%1$s&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;widget %2$s&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&#39;,
    &#39;after_widget&#39;  =&amp;gt; &#39;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;&#39;,
    &#39;before_title&#39;  =&amp;gt; &#39;&amp;lt;h2 class=&amp;quot;widgettitle&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&#39;,
    &#39;after_title&#39;   =&amp;gt; &#39;&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;&#39; 
); ?&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;parameters&#34;&gt;Parameters&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;name – Sidebar name (default is localized ‘Sidebar’ and numeric ID).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;id – Sidebar id – Must be all in lowercase, with no spaces (default is a numeric auto-incremented ID).
description – Text description of what/where the sidebar is. Shown on widget management screen. (Since 2.9) (default: empty)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;class – CSS class name to assign to the widget HTML (default: empty).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;before_widget – HTML to place before every widget(default: &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;li id=&amp;quot;%1$s&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;widget %2$s&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;) Note: uses sprintf for variable substitution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;after_widget – HTML to place after every widget (default: &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;\n&lt;/code&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;before_title – HTML to place before every title (default: &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h2 class=&amp;quot;widgettitle&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;after_title – HTML to place after every title (default: &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;\n&lt;/code&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is best served with an example. Suppose you want to have a custom sidebar for your ‘about’ page that details contact information. If it were me, I’d add the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;?php register_sidebar( array(
    &#39;name&#39;          =&amp;gt; __( &#39;About Sidebar&#39;, &#39;whateveryourthemeis&#39; ),
    &#39;id&#39;            =&amp;gt; &#39;sidebar-about&#39;,
    &#39;description&#39;   =&amp;gt; __( &#39;Appears on the About page&#39;),
    &#39;before_widget&#39; =&amp;gt; &#39;&amp;lt;li id=&amp;quot;%1$s&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;widget %2$s&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&#39;,
    &#39;after_widget&#39;  =&amp;gt; &#39;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;&#39;,
    &#39;before_title&#39;  =&amp;gt; &#39;&amp;lt;h3 class=&amp;quot;about-sidebar&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&#39;,
    &#39;after_title&#39;   =&amp;gt; &#39;&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;&#39; 
); ?&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bits that say &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; will vary depending on your theme. In the Twenty Twelve theme, they’re &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;aside&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; respectively. Change each instance to what it is for the other sidebars in your theme; this will help keep a consistent look for your sidebars. For the sidebar’s ID, make sure it is something along the lines of ‘sidebar-whateverthesidebarisabout’. This is important for later. Make sure to put this before the closing } for the themename_widgets_init() function.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upload your new/modified functions.php file to your webhost (you can use something like Filezilla to do so). If you go now to Appearance then Widgets, you’ll see your new sidebar to the right, grouped right below with the others. You can add widgets to it, although nothing will show up yet on any of your pages. To change that, we need to create a new template file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;creating-the-template-file&#34;&gt;Creating the template file&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In your theme folder, there should also be a sidebar.php file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;?php
/**
* The sidebar containing the main widget area.
*
* If no active widgets in sidebar, let&#39;s hide it completely.
*
* @package depends on your theme
* @subpackage ditto
* @since same
*/
?&amp;gt;

    &amp;lt;?php if ( is_active_sidebar( &#39;sidebar-1&#39; ) ) : ?&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;div id=&amp;quot;secondary&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;widget-area&amp;quot; role=&amp;quot;complementary&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
            &amp;lt;?php dynamic_sidebar( &#39;sidebar-1&#39; ); ?&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- #secondary --&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;?php endif; ?&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure to look at your own and substitute accordingly. Luckily, the code here is very easily to modify. In the above code, you would change the instances of ‘1’ to ‘about’ for our example, so it would look like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;?php if ( is_active_sidebar( &#39;sidebar-about&#39; ) ) : ?&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;div id=&amp;quot;secondary&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;widget-area&amp;quot; role=&amp;quot;complementary&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;?php dynamic_sidebar( &#39;sidebar-about&#39; ); ?&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- #secondary --&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;?php endif; ?&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What this code will do is display your widgets if there are any, and display nothing if there are none for whatever reason. Upload this file too to your theme directory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;include&#34;&gt;Include&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the fun part, building a template for you to use your sidebar on. Much of this is self-explanatory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;?php
/**
* Template Name: About
*
* Description: Template for the About page
*
* @package whatever
* @subpackage your
* @since theme_says
**/


get_header(); ?&amp;gt;

    &amp;lt;section id=&amp;quot;primary&amp;quot; class=&amp;quot;site-content right-content&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
        &amp;lt;div id=&amp;quot;content&amp;quot; role=&amp;quot;main&amp;quot;&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will be the first bit of your template, you can name it whatever you like (page-whatever.php usually). The &lt;strong&gt;Template Name&lt;/strong&gt; will be whatever you select in the drop-down menu for your Page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This next bit is verbatim from page.php. It’s what allows the content you type when editing the post to show up in your page. You can read up on get_template_part() if you wish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;?php while ( have_posts() ) : the_post(); ?&amp;gt;
            &amp;lt;?php get_template_part( &#39;content&#39;, &#39;page&#39; ); ?&amp;gt;
            &amp;lt;?php comments_template( &#39;&#39;, true ); ?&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;?php endwhile; // end of the loop. ?&amp;gt;      
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first line takes the content from content-page.php, and the second is the comments template.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To finish it up, add&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;            &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- #content --&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;/section&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- #primary --&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;?php get_sidebar(&#39;about&#39;); ?&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;?php get_footer(); ?&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The part in parentheses (‘about’) will change depending on the ID of your sidebar, back in the functions.php file. Now you can upload page-about.php to your webhost. If you’ve done it correctly, when you go to create a new page, you should see your new template in the template options.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>