<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on Jessica Huynh</title>
    <link>/categories/recipes/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on Jessica Huynh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/categories/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Gỏi cuốn and peanut sauce recipe</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/07/goi-cuon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 22:22:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/07/goi-cuon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gỏi cuốn are Vietnamese spring rolls; they&amp;rsquo;re easy to make, especially for group things. This is an appropriate-for-cheap-college students version of a recipe I learned from my mom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not giving any particular amounts because I never measure things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;vietnamese-spring-rolls-gỏi-cuốn&#34;&gt;Vietnamese spring rolls (Gỏi cuốn)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bánh tráng (rice paper wrappers)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Miến (mung bean and potato noodles); in the US they&amp;rsquo;re often in a tell-tale pink mesh wrap. If you can&amp;rsquo;t find them, regular rice noodles will do&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sliced cucumbers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grated carrots&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lettuce or cabbage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Generally, about 10 ounces of noodles will serve for a packet of wrappers. One grated carrot can usually do around 5 goi cuon. Cucumbers vary a little bit more but one cucumber per about ten goi cuon works for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also add, depending on dietary requirements and restrictions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cooked shrimp (most traditional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chicken (I marinate with soy sauce, lemon, ginger, and garlic in some proportion I haven&amp;rsquo;t figured out yet)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tofu&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re fancy and have money (neither apply for me), the most traditional things to add are pork slices called chả and/or poached beef. Egg is also a popular option, although I&amp;rsquo;ve never tried it myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure everything is cut and sliced properly and fill a large bowl with water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wet the wrapper in the bowl of water by dipping one part in, then turning it in a circle all the way around&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lay the wrapper on a plate and at the very bottom of the wrapper towards you, lay some lettuce/cabbage pointing horizontally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Layer the noodles, cucumber, and cabbage on top&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fold over the wrapper from the bottom so that it covers just the ingredients you&amp;rsquo;ve added&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you have a meat or tofu to add, place them in a row just above the folded-over portion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fold the sides of the wrapper over so that nothing can escape&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From the bottom, now that the sides are folded over to contain the filling, continue rolling until everything is rolled up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repeat for as many spring rolls as you want&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;peanut-sauce&#34;&gt;Peanut sauce&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know the ingredients look fishy but I swear this tastes just as good as anything you&amp;rsquo;ll find in a restaurant or bakery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients-1&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Peanut butter (chunky or not doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tương đen (Hoison sauce)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Garlic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tương ớt tỏi (Vietnamese chili garlic sauce)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Water&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do two tablespoons of hoison sauce and peanut butter for every cup of water. You can add sugar and mashed up peanuts too, if that&amp;rsquo;s your preference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions-1&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Put in the peanut butter and hoison sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add water and stir until the peanut butter clumps are no longer visible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add as much garlic and chili sauce as you feel appropriate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>